

CONTACT

- +372 56254513
- Aimarkiivits1@gmail.com
- Tartu, Estonia

EDUCATION

2022 - Present
TARTU VOCATIONAL COLLEGE

2021 - 2022 VÕNNU SECONDARY SCHOOL

2012 - 2021 VÕNNU PRIMARY SCHOOL

SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML/CSS
- React.js
- Express.js
- MySQL

LANGUAGES

- Estonian Native Language
- English C2

AIMAR KIIVITS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am Aimar Kiivits, a 19 year old from Tartu, Estonia. I am currently studying software development at VOCO, aka Tartu Vocational College. I have always had an interest in computers, and after trying out programming during a school event, I realized that I wanted to learn more. I enjoy board games, video games, and challenging my brain with puzzles. To stay physically active, I train in Olympic weightlifting four times a week.

WORK EXPERIENCE

AS Eesti Post

06. 2024 - 08. 2024

Early morning Newspaper Delivery

• Worked here over summer break to earn some extra money.

AS Olerex

10. 2023 - 06. 2024

Customer Service

 Worked here part time during the school year to earn money and get some work experience